To whom it may concern,

I yield a distinguishing blend of determination, ambition, and ingenuity. I am confident that I can be a productive member of your team. I excel in a team environment and exhibit exceptional communication skills. I have a great reputation with references to prove my abilities.

I am looking for a career opportunity where I can utilize my skills, education, and dedication. I believe I can be a valuable asset to your company. I am currently employed with a technology company in Bend, OR.

If it appears that my qualifications meet your needs, I would be happy to discuss my background in a personal meeting. I will be looking forward to meeting with you in the future to follow up on the status of my application. Thank you for your time.

Sincerely,

Justin Jones justinbjones87@gmail.com (530) 526 0525

JUSTIN B JONES

61369 Whitetail St Bend, OR 97702 (530) 526 - 0525 justinbjones87@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a motivated production-oriented developer with valuable experience in the information technology and customer service industries. I am a very apt learner with an exceptional reputation and impeccable desire to progress in any environment.

QUALIFICATIONS

- Microsoft Certified Technology Specialist
- Proficient in multiple technologies: C#, .Net, C++, Python, PHP, JavaScript
- Extensive experience with SQL Server and other DBMS
- History of consistently meeting goals and delivering a high level of job performance

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

BMS Technologies, Bend OR Developer, June 2014 – Present

Responsibilities include, but not limited to, the ongoing development and administration of multiple web application including https://bendmailing.com/ and https://bendmailing.com/

County of Humboldt - Information Technology, Eureka CA Developer, June 2013 – July 2014

Responsibilities include, but not limited to, custom application development, building complex stored procedures while concurrently performing webmaster and minute DBA duties.

BizTech, Eureka CA

Developer, Dec 2012 - June 2014

Responsibilities include, but not limited to, LAN configurations, POS systems, and ground-up design and development of multiple internally used client-specific web applications pertaining to resource-management and reporting services.

EDUCATION

Humboldt State University, Arcata, Ca B.S., Computer Science with Business Administration Minor - May 2014